<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Complainist</title>
  <link href="http://complainist.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://complainist.com/"/>
  <updated>2011-10-31T10:25:57-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://complainist.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Linda Wilson</name>
    <email></email>
  </author>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Katadyn Water Filter</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/water-filter"/>
    <updated>2012-10-31T10:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/katadyn-water-filter-reply-2.markdown</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Alan,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I owe you an apology. I misunderstood your previous email, and assumed Katadyn would be flying my family to Switzerland for testing. I'm embarrassed to admit that I already started packing and learning the language. My daughter was excited to visit IKEA headquarters, too. This news will be disappointing to my whole family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of questions will you need to ask my son? He is a very curious eight year old, and I'm sure he will be excited to talk to someone from another country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand your need to get more information on this matter, and appreciate your persistence. I referred to my husband's expert diagnosis in a previous email, is there other documentation that he should provide? He could write something up using official university letterhead describing Aaron's symptoms, if that would help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, I'm so sorry about the travel misunderstanding. Or as the Swedish say, Så lessen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Katadyn Water Filter</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/water-filter"/>
    <updated>2012-10-31T09:39:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/katadyn-water-filter-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linda,
I must assume that you are kidding.  Did you read my message to you?  There are many ways that a person can get sick and have the symptoms that your son had.  If, after reading all of the potential reasons, including your son carefully reading the manual and taking all precautions, you still truly believe that the filter may be to blame, I offered to perhaps test the filter.  There is no scenario where we will fly your son to Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, before proceeding, we’ll need to talk to your son to learn more.  Also, we would need to learn what a doctor said and review test results since with this serious situation, we assume that you had him tested by a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is to review the results that you received from a doctor before we proceed. And, if we proceed in any way, it would involve returning your Hiker to us for careful examination and potential testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Alan Lizee&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Katadyn Water Filter</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/water-filter"/>
    <updated>2012-10-31T08:12:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/katadyn-water-filter-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Alan,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for your reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aaron is doing much better. There were a couple of days where things weren't looking good, but his color is finally returning, and he's regaining some of his appetite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Aaron first fell ill, my husband (who is a doctor) found a substitute teacher to teach his Intro To Biology class so he could take care of Aaron. He seemed to think his illness had something to do with some bacteria that the filter didn't catch, if that helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really appreciate your willingness to try and get to the bottom of this situation. When is a good time for us to fly into Switzerland to get Aaron examined in your laboratory? Does Katadyn have private jets, or will be be flying with one of the major airlines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of tests will need to be run? If his symptoms subside before our flight, is that all right? I'll be in Milwaukee in a few days for work, and I could stop by the stockyards and collect some more water, if that would help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Katadyn Water Filter: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/water-filter"/>
    <updated>2012-10-28T18:43:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/katadyn-water-filter-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your inquiry is important and I hope that your son is doing better.  It’s unfortunate that this coincided with the Science Fair that was so important to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To answer your questions, each Katadyn Hiker is tested at the factory prior to shipment.  While I guess it is possible that a contamination could occur in an outlet hose, we have not seen this in 10+ years of Hiker production.  We very rarely hear of people getting sick but when we ask return questions, our experience has been that the illness seems to come from other causes.  Following are some questions that we ask:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Was he tested by a Doctor?  This will often point the cause in a right direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did he sanitize his hands carefully after using the bathroom?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did any untreated water touch his hands, lips or edge of water container?  This would especially be true in ground water in a stocklyard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Was the output hose ever in contact with contaminated water?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In his case, did anyone else get sick during this field trip?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Our intent is not to pass any blame but to identify that there are many ways that people can get sick.  For people who camp, for example, it is common thought that far more people get sick from unsanitary conditions (not washing hands) than bad food or water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another comment - hopefully, your son read the product instructions carefully and, as they suggest, used it at home before using it in the field.  Especially when potentially contaminated water from a puddle at a stockyard.  While these products can do great things, they typically are used in rivers, lakes etc.  In unusually challenging conditions, the instructions say that it is always prudent to use a purification tablet in addition to a filter of any brand.  No water filter will remove all viruses, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a separate note, I’m curious about the made in Sweden question.  Our products are not produced in Sweden.  All Katadyn Hikers are made in Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will replace your Hiker if you want.  If you still believe that the filter may be the cause, we can communicate further and perhaps agree to send it back to Switzerland and have it tested in our laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, again my condolences to your son.  Please let me know how you would like us to proceed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Alan Lizee&lt;br/&gt;
Chairman&lt;br/&gt;
Katadyn North America&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Katadyn Water Filter</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/water-filter"/>
    <updated>2012-10-25T20:15:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/katadyn-water-filter</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Katadyn,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have recently become concerned over the impurities in public drinking water, and did research on the most environmentally friendly microfilter I could use to protect my children from bacterial dangers. I recently purchased one of your Hiker model Katadyn microfilters and was very excited to start being more environmentally conscious, while at the same time enjoying natural and pure water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My youngest son, Aaron, went on a class field trip to the stockyards in Milwaukee last week, and I sent him off with our new water filter in his lunch sack, along with a sandwich and a fruit rollup. During the lunch break, Aaron found some water that had collected on the ground, and filtered it using the water filter. To my astonishment, he became violently ill later that night, and was so sick the next day that he missed the Science Fair. Aaron was very upset, because he had worked awfully hard on his project on bacterial growth, and no one got to see the bacterial colonies that he grew from a culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it possible that we received a contaminated outlet hose from the factory? I noticed on the unit that it said &quot;made in Sweden&quot;, and I have a Swedish friend who never washes her hands after using the lavatory. Have your other customers had similar problems with this unit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>TurboTax</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/turbotax"/>
    <updated>2010-04-13T20:38:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/turbotax</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear TurboTax,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am trying to use your product this year to complete my tax filing as my 2010 New Year's resolution is to embrace technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I am pleased with how easy it is enter my tax information, I have some concerns with my results. When I entered the site, I was notified that the service would cost me $49.95. However, I am about to file my taxes and the website is telling me it wants to pay me $1,650.00 dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be some sort of error in your program&amp;mdash;I would just like to pay the fee to use your service to file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also concerned that this will cause me to file my taxes late. Can I get written permission from you to allow me to be a day or two late on my tax return?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,  &lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Please respond quickly&amp;mdash;taxes are due on April 15th this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Clue: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/clue"/>
    <updated>2010-03-09T10:54:24-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/clue-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Stephanie,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for you response.  I am interested in finding a more appropriate game for my son to play, but am concerned that &quot;Clue Carnival: The Case Of The Missing Prizes&quot; might encourage stealing, as the original clue seems to have encouraged some violent tendencies in my young son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently he started playing an incredibly violent game on his Wii called &quot;Chicken Shooter&quot;, which features execution-style slaughterings of innocent animals. To make matters worse, I found a dead chicken in our chicken coop yesterday, and I can't help but suspect Aaron. Is this normal?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate the offer to exchange my copy of Clue.  Do you think the game could be modified in the next two years to be more appropriate for younger children?  If not, I may as well keep my current copy and only bring it out again when Aaron is at an appropriate age to handle the mature content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,  &lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Would you please forward my original email to your game developers?  I believe there is some value in the surprise party version of Clue I described.  I started creating my own version at home, but have had trouble finding a miniature kazoo for one of the game pieces. Perhaps your developers might be able to suggest an appropriate place to purchase such things.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Clue: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/clue"/>
    <updated>2010-03-05T18:57:35-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/clue-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting us regarding Hasbro's Clue game. We appreciate your taking the time to bring this matter to our attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hasbro, Inc. prides itself on its excellent reputation, based on years of experience in planning, designing and constructing safe, dependable and age appropriate products. We do count on parents such as you to help us maintain the high standards we keep for parents and their children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you alluded to, the Clue game is age coded 8 and up and our recommendation is that 8 plus children play. We do manufacture a Clue game that is ages 5 and up. This game is Clue Carnival: The Case of the Missing Prizes. Please visit our web site to see this game, as well as, other games that are appropriate for your child's age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your convenience, we will be sending a postage paid label to assist you in returning the Clue game to us. Our postage paid labels are valid for four weeks from the date of the letter. As soon as we receive the game, we will forward it to our Quality Assurance team for further evaluation, and a replacement product of comparable value will be sent. Due to your concern, in the meantime, please discontinue use of the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please call us at 1(888) 836-7025 if we can be of further assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you for contacting us.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Blockbuster Video</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/blockbuster"/>
    <updated>2010-03-02T16:09:57-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/blockbuster-video-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Maricar,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh dear, am I already in trouble?  I do not want to provide my account information, as I fear that you may suspend it due to my recent actions.  I did not intend to steal from Blockbuster, and hope we can resolve this matter without involving the authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I need to do to continue being a valued Blockbuster customer?  How much additional money do I need to pay in order to own &quot;Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Squeakquel&quot;?  Hopefully after purchasing the movie in full, we can consider this matter resolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Blockbuster Video</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/blockbuster"/>
    <updated>2010-03-02T16:09:06-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/blockbuster-video-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting Blockbuster Customer Care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that you saw an FBI message at the beginning of one of the films: &quot;DVD FOR SALE ONLY&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am however unable to pull up your account using the e-mail address that you have provided - as well as your name. So that I would be able to assist you better and for the speedy resolution of your concern, please provide additional information such as your account number, your address with the zip code and the phone number associated with your account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you have any other concerns, please feel free to contact us anytime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maricar
Blockbuster Customer Care&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Clue</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/clue"/>
    <updated>2010-03-02T14:58:16-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/clue</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Parker Brothers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last Sunday I caught my youngest son, Aaron, playing Clue with his friends in our rumpus room after I had finished cleaning up after his birthday party. I loved playing Clue as a child, so when Aaron had some questions about the gameplay, I was happy to assist. While paging through the rulebook, I noticed that the listed age range was &quot;8 and up&quot;, which brings me to the reason for this letter. My son is six, and his friends range from the age of five and a half to seven. I'm afraid the violent nature of the game may be damaging to children younger than the recommended age range. What changes should I watch for in my son to assure he hasn't been affected by this game? What experiences have other customers had?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven't broken the news to his friends' parents yet, as I thought I would consult with you first. Needless to say, I have confiscated the game, and will only allow him to play it when he has reached the age of eight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you thought about creating a Clue-type game more appropriate for young children? How about a game where you have to solve who threw the surprise party in what room, and using what party favor? The options could be streamers, party hats, kazoos, and balloons. You could even reuse the same game board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, do you have any recommendations for currently available board games more appropriate for a six year old?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,  &lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mighty Putty: Response #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/mighty-putty"/>
    <updated>2010-02-19T14:48:57-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/mighty-putty-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was forwarded your email about our product, Mighty Putty. I'm afraid that you have us confused with the product Silly Putty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;br/&gt;
Cheryl&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Response #5</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-17T18:49:11-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-response-5</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your additional concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are very sorry, but the call center phones are automated and will not accept calls after 8:00 PM Central Standard Time. As we stated in our previous email, please contact a Member Services Representative at 1-800-651-6000.  Weight Watchers National Customer Service Center is open Monday through Thursday from 7:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m. CST, Friday 7:00 a.m. - 7:00 p.m. CST and Saturday 7:00 a.m. - 3:00 p.m. CST.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Kurli
Customer Service Associate
Weight Watchers International,  Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mighty Putty: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/mighty-putty"/>
    <updated>2010-02-16T15:16:13-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/mighty-putty-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh dear, that is very disappointing to hear, but makes sense now that I think about it.  When I left it out on the counter, my son kept playing with it and tried making impressions of my car keys. I called him away to help me clean up his room, and when I came back the putty had hardened around the car keys.  Do you know how I can remove it?  I can't start my car, and I have an appointment I need to be getting to soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you still sell the silly variety of your putty?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mighty Putty: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/mighty-putty"/>
    <updated>2010-02-16T15:14:32-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/mighty-putty-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your eMail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please be advised that this putty IS NOT the silly putty of yesteryear. It is an epoxy used to glue things together. It is not intended to be used by a child. If it dries to something it will not come off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You'll need to return it to the store where you purchased it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Customer Service
Plymouth Direct&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Reply #4</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-16T13:04:57-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-reply-4</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Kurli,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your hours this week?  Would it be possible for someone to stay until 8:30pm so I can get some help without incurring an overage fee?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mighty Putty</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/mighty-putty"/>
    <updated>2010-02-16T12:57:37-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/mighty-putty</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mighty Putty,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have great memories of playing with your putty as a child, so when I saw your product in the store the other day, I bought it for my son, Aaron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to find transferring Archie comics particularly enjoyable, so I pulled out my husband's vintage newspaper comic collection to demonstrate.  Unfortunately, my demonstration failed and resulted in a ripped newspaper, a disappointed son, and an extremely angry husband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm wondering if I received a defective product, or if I'm doing something incorrectly?  I noticed that this putty no longer comes in a plastic egg, and am wondering if that somehow affected the shelf life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, do you know where I can get a copy of the June, 4th, 1967 Chicago Tribune printing of Archie?  It's the one where Jughead enters an eating contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Response #4</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-11T19:21:23-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-response-4</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for getting back to Weight Watchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to contact a Member Services Representative at 1-800-651-6000.  Weight Watchers National Customer Service Center is open Monday through Thursday from 7:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m. CST, Friday 7:00 a.m. - 7:00 p.m. CST and Saturday 7:00 a.m. - 3:00 p.m. CST.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Kurli &lt;br/&gt;
Customer Service Associate&lt;br/&gt;
Weight Watchers International,  Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Reply #3</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-11T11:51:24-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-reply-3</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Ivonne,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried calling yesterday evening, but your offices were closed. How late is customer support open?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would prefer calling in the evening, as I get free minutes on my phone after 8pm. I would call during the day, but I've used all of my anytime minutes up this month talking to my mother, who is currently battling a nasty virus, and the next time I have free minutes available is when my new billing cycle starts, which is in March.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would hate to leave this issue unresolved that long, as my son has a birthday party coming up next week, and has requested that we return to that same pizza parlor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Response #3</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-10T17:19:40-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-response-3</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting us with your inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please call: 1/800-651-6000 and a Member Services Representative will be happy to assist you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Ivonne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer Service Associate&lt;br/&gt;
Weight Watchers International,  Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Reply #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-09T12:25:58-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-reply-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Kurli,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your response.  I thought I was already signed up for Weight Watchers online, but perhaps I am mistaken.  I've been having some trouble with my credit card lately, so I'm wondering if it got declined when signing up, which would explain why you can't find my information. Do you accept Diner's club?  What information do I need to provide you in order to become an online subscriber and get my question answered?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure who you are referring to when you said it would best to consult with my Leader. How can I contact them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Do you have any good recommendations for food scales?  I read on the online forums that having one helps in measuring portion sizes and calculating points.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Response #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-08T22:21:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting us with your inquiry.  As we stated in our previous email, the online Customer Service Team is here primarily to provide technical support to Weight WatchersÂ® Online subscribers and to answer general questions about meetings and other services.  We do not have the proper experience to address your specific weight loss questions.  Therefore, it would be best to consult with your Leader regarding any concerns you may have after you join Weight Watchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Kurli
Customer Service Associate&lt;br/&gt;
Weight Watchers International,  Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-06T16:10:56-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Renatta,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have not been able to attend a meeting in person yet, as the closest Weight Watchers meeting location is 15 miles away, and my car has been acting up lately, so I haven't been able to drive further than a few miles away from my home. I hope to attend a meeting as soon as I have time to take my car over to my long time mechanic, Lyle Christiansen, for its regular service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm interested in using the internet for support if possible, but I'm not quite sure which message board to post my question regarding the predicament I described. &quot;What I Ate Today&quot; seemed like a good choice, but now that some time is passed since the incident, writing about what I ate a week ago doesn't seem appropriate.  Do you have suggestions for the best forum to handle such a question?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-02-06T15:27:24-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We apologize if our response was delayed. This is a busy time of year for us and our e-mail volume is very high. We appreciate your patience during this busy time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Linda,
Thank you for contacting WeightWatchers.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Customer Service Team is here primarily to provide technical support for subscribers to Weight Watchers Online Products. We are, however, also available to answer general questions about Weight Watchers Meetings and other services. Unfortunately, we do not have the proper experience to answer your weight-loss question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our long history, we've found that the best support for people in need of assistance with weight loss can be found at Weight Watchers Meetings. To locate a Meeting near you, please use the Meeting Finder on our site. (Please note that the cost of attending meetings is not included in a subscription to Weight Watchers Online.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the Community section of our site allows you to correspond with other people who are using Weight Watchers to help them lose weight. It's a great place for tip sharing and inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br/&gt;
Renata&lt;br/&gt;
Customer Service Associate&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Weight Watchers</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/weight-watchers"/>
    <updated>2010-01-29T15:23:41-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/weight-watchers</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Weight Watchers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've been a member for a few months now, and it's been really helpful having the support and tools to help me control my weight.  I have a couple of questions I'm hoping someone can answer, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last Wednesday was my birthday, and a few friends and I went out to a local pizza parlor to celebrate.  I ate several slices of pizza, making sure to track my points. I indulged, and had about 20 points worth of pizza, causing me to have to dip into my flex points.  Later that night I didn't feel well, and eventually threw up my dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does this affect my points?  Do I get those 20 points back? Does it depend on how much I threw up?  Because if so, I threw up about 1 and 3/4 cups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Blockbuster Video</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/blockbuster"/>
    <updated>2010-01-04T18:54:39-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/blockbuster-video</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Blockbuster,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently rented some movies from you over the weekend and saw a disturbing FBI message at the beginning of one of the films: &quot;DVD FOR SALE ONLY&quot;.  I do not want to get in trouble with the FBI, as I have had some tax problems in the past, and do not want to press my luck.  What do I need to do to safely resolve this situation?  Can I purchase the film in question from you for the original cost minus the cost of the rental (which I already paid)?  Will that be enough to keep me out of trouble?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, are you going to get in trouble from the government for renting a DVD that's clearly meant for sale only, or did you simply mix up DVDs you had for sale and DVDs you had for rent?  For what it's worth, I will not say anything to the FBI about this matter, as I enjoy your video store very much and would not want to see it closed down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Polish Nail Spa</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/polish-nail-spa"/>
    <updated>2009-12-22T13:51:31-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/polish-nail-spa</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Polish Nail Spa,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My family is hosting a foreign exchange student from Poland for the next few months, and I'm looking for things for her to do in town that might make her feel more at home. What types of services you offer that might suit a Polish customer? Do you serve any Polish themed foods during nail care, or play any Polish music?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Covert Ford: Response #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/covert-ford"/>
    <updated>2008-08-31T20:58:55-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/covert-ford-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mrs Wilson,  we can do this purchase any way you want to do it.  We would love to help you surprise your husband!  Call me at [XXX-XXXX] when you get a chance.  I won't be in the office until about 10.00 this am.  Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title> Covert Ford: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/covert-ford"/>
    <updated>2008-08-31T18:23:10-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/covert-auto-responses-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linda- Sure! I've been here for over a decade and could regal you with lots of fun gift purchases/surprises. Let's start with what kind of dream truck you're looking for ? cell [XXX-XXXX] or e-mail . Ready to surprise!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Covert Ford</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/covert-ford"/>
    <updated>2008-08-25T23:38:14-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/covert-ford</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Covert Ford,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband's birthday is coming up shortly, and he's been wanting a new truck for some time now.  Since I'd like this to be a surprise, I thought Covert Ford would be a good choice of dealership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I commit to purchasing, though, I'd like more information about the secrecy-related services you offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can the car be delivered to our house sometime between midnight and 5am (when my husband will surely be asleep)? Also, is it possible to pay for the car after my husband has received it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Free Whitepaper: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/free-whitepaper"/>
    <updated>2008-08-06T23:21:41-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/free-whitepaper-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We refer to white papers as a guide or report to help inform potential customers on a specific product or service we offer. I apologize if this was not clear in our advertisement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim&lt;br/&gt;
E-Commerce Support&lt;br/&gt;
CDW&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Free Whitepaper</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/free-whitepaper"/>
    <updated>2008-08-06T12:19:41-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/free-whitepaper</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear CDW,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently saw your online advertisement for &quot;free whitepaper&quot; while I was browsing for a birthday present for my husband, and was intruiged.  Not being one to pass up a good deal, I clicked on the link and printed out the suggested files.  To my surprise, when the paper came out of my printer it already had writing on it.  Was this an error on my part, or is your link incorrect?  I was expecting plain white paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br/&gt;
Linda B Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S.  Do you offer free colored paper, too?  I'm doing an art project and am in need of some colorful paper. Neon green, specifically.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Melted M&amp;Ms: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/m-and-ms"/>
    <updated>2008-05-16T14:48:17-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/melted-mms-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear M&amp;amp;Ms,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your speedy response, but I fear that you have misunderstood my problem.  The M&amp;amp;Ms in question were not in my hand at the time, but in my back pocket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't think the candy shell melted, either, it just cracked and let the melted chocolate ooze out, staining my favorite pair of desert survival pants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I now see that your melting guarantee doesn't cover the candies while not in hands or mouths, I'm concerned that other customers might make the same mistake, causing them to have an unfortunate experience similar to mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would it be possible to put a warning on future bags of M&amp;amp;Ms warning customers that severe melting could occur if kept in pants pockets for extended periods of time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Do Peanut M&amp;amp;Ms suffer from the same problems as the plain variety?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Melted M&amp;Ms: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/m-and-ms"/>
    <updated>2008-05-14T15:22:09-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/melted-mms-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our advertising slogan actually reads; &quot;THE MILK CHOCOLATE MELTS IN YOUR MOUTH-NOT IN YOUR HANDS.&quot;  The objective of our advertising is to acquaint consumers with the fact that the candies are neat to eat under average conditions because they have a thin sugar shell protecting the chocolate centers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that the &quot;melting&quot; you described pertains to the sugar shell coating of the candies. Sometimes the pure food colors will rub off when they come in contact with moisture in the hands -- especially if the candy is held for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Melted M&amp;Ms</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/m-and-ms"/>
    <updated>2008-05-12T10:30:55-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/mandms</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear M&amp;amp;Ms,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I once saw a commercial that claimed that your candy only melted inside mouths, so when I was searching for snacks for my recent desert survival retreat, I chose M&amp;amp;Ms.  On our trip, I slipped a handful of your candies into my back pocket to keep myself energized for our long hike, but after a few hours my hike-mates started giving me strange looks, often asking if I was feeling all right.  I realized what they were thinking later, when I discovered that the candies had melted completely, leaving a suspicious brown stain on my rear end.  Needless to say, I was mortified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My attempts to keep the candies cool by putting them inside our water jug were fruitless, as they eventually dissolved and contaminated the jug.  Later, when my hike-mate left her jug of water at our previous campsite, we had to rely on the melted M&amp;amp;M tainted drinking water for our primary water source.  Unfortunately, the sugary water dried us all out more than aided us, and some of us suffered the ill effects of severe dehydration.  We ended up having to cut our trip short, due to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this normal?   I am wondering if you might have a candy that withstands greater temperatures, or if I just received a defective bag of M&amp;amp;Ms?  Would skittles have been a better desert snack?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tostitos Scoops: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/tostitos-scoops"/>
    <updated>2007-11-30T10:23:44-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/tostitos-scoops-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We appreciate your comments.  We do our best to provide consumers with a wide
variety of great-tasting snack food choices.  Our chips are made to accompany
regular dips for chips, not a texture as thick as ice cream.  Your feedback and
concerns will be relayed to our Research and Marketing Teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of us at Frito-Lay appreciate your interest and hope you will continue to
reach for Frito-Lay products whenever you are looking for great tasting snacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frito-Lay Consumer Affairs&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tostitos Scoops</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/tostitos-scoops"/>
    <updated>2007-11-29T11:04:57-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/tostitos-scoops</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Tostitos,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a bag of your &quot;Scoops&quot; tortilla chips, and was disappointed at how easily they break while scooping.  I have tried several different brands of ice cream with no luck -- the chips simply will not scoop satisfactorily.  Would you recommend a different product for this purpose, or do you think the problem is with the ice cream I'm using?  I have found that letting the ice cream melt for a little while improves matters, but I have yet to be fully satisfied.  I am hoping you sell a stronger chip, that would better suit my needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S.  I would try using frozen yogurt, but my daughter is allergic.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Force Flex Trash Bags</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/force-flex-trash-bags"/>
    <updated>2007-09-26T15:03:10-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/force-flex-trash-bags-email-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Glad,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently my family and I organized a neighborhood cleanup after our neighbor's house was vandalized by a local gang. We chose to use your Force Flex bags to gather up the debris because of the highly-acclaimed &quot;puncture protection&quot; your brand offers, while other brands do not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the shards of broken glass and several boards with nails were no match for these bags. I was disappointed and embarrassed that the bags I publicly supported broke and spilled their contents in front of all my neighbors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering if the bags I purchased are defective, or if Iâ€™m using them incorrectly? Should I have double bagged? Do you have a product that is designed to withstand greater force?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Brookstone Gas Grill Cover: Response #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/brookstone-gas-grill-cover"/>
    <updated>2007-07-31T12:08:18-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/brookstone-gas-grill-cover-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Ms. Wilson,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, we do not carry the product you have requested, nor do we have a similar product that may suit the same needs or a specific resource to refer you to. We regret that we cannot be of assistance to you at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We appreciate your interest in Brookstone products and hope that we can be of service to you in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Elisha&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brookstone.com Customer Service&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Brookstone Gas Grill Cover: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/brookstone-gas-grill-cover"/>
    <updated>2007-07-31T09:50:38-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/brookstone-gas-grill-cover-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm very disappointed to hear that, but it makes sense now that I think about it.  If the cover was designed for use while grilling, it would be able to handle the heat without melting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still interested in protecting my grill while cooking, though.  Do you offer a product that has higher tolerance for heat, perhaps with vent holes?  I would really like to keep my grill in good condition.  It would also be great if that product came in green, like the one I have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your help,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Brookstone Gas Grill Cover: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/brookstone-gas-grill-cover"/>
    <updated>2007-07-31T09:36:49-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/brookstone-gas-grill-cover-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Ms. Wilson,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We apologize you have experienced problems using your grill cover. The cover is intended to be used ONLY while you are not grilling. The intentions are for it to protect your grill from the weather elements. Please make sure you take the grill cover off when you plan on grilling to avoid further damage to your cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please let us know if we may be of further assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Elisha&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brookstone.com Customer Service&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Brookstone Gas Grill Cover</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/brookstone-gas-grill-cover"/>
    <updated>2007-07-30T11:36:08-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/brookstone-gas-grill-cover</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Brookstone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brookstone.com/store/product.asp?product_code=356931&amp;wid=18&amp;cid=1803&amp;sid=180303&amp;search_type=subcategory&amp;prodtemp=t1&quot;&gt;Rectangular Gas Grill Cover&lt;/a&gt; to protect my new Weber grill, and while I am pleased with the overall look of the cover, I have had some trouble using it while grilling.  Although it fits snugly when the grill is closed, opening the grill is difficult while the cover is in place.  I managed to prevent it from slipping by fastening it more securely to the grill with some duct tape, but I do feel a better attachment mechanism should be included with the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, when grilling, smoke seems to gather under the cover and pour out of the bottom making the meat very difficult to see.  The heat generated by the grill also seems to be a problem, as the cover has melted slightly in places.  I'm wondering if some venting might help, or if you sell a more durable version of this grill cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are the problems I've described common with this product, or am I simply grilling at a higher temperature than recommended?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tempur-Pedic: Action Taken</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/tempur-pedic"/>
    <updated>2004-06-03T11:26:10-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/tempur-pedic-action-taken</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As of June 2003, Tempur-pedic's new commercials now do not use the &quot;glass of red wine&quot; example, but rather a &quot;glass of water&quot; example.  We have made a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tempur-Pedic: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/tempur-pedic"/>
    <updated>2003-11-03T00:00:17-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/tempur-pedic-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately we can no offer any compensation for this.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tempur-Pedic</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/tempur-pedic"/>
    <updated>2003-11-01T11:24:28-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/tempur-pedic</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Tempur-Pedic,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently saw your commercial advertising your pressure relieving mattresses. In the commercial, the man explained that on your mattress you can place a glass of red wine and jump on the bed without spilling the wine. You then suggested &quot;try THAT on your metal spring mattress&quot;. I did as the commercial suggested and was very disappointed in the results. The wine spilled and permanently stained my bed! I was wondering if your company would be willing to offer some sort of compensation or discount on one of your spill resistant mattresses to remedy this unfortunate situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,  &lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Easy Bake Oven: Response #2</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/easy-bake-oven"/>
    <updated>2003-01-25T00:00:43-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/easy-bake-oven-response-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ms. Wilson, Your email concerning a recent incident with with your daughter's Easy Bake Oven has been forwarded to me for response but didn't have a phone number for you. Please call me at 1-800-XXX-7276, ext.
XXXX at your convenience to discuss. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine M----n&lt;br/&gt;
Office of Corporate Compliance&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Easy Bake Oven: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/easy-bake-oven"/>
    <updated>2003-01-22T11:22:48-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/easy-bake-oven-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi Linda,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting Hasbro, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are sharing your question with those internal parties who are more
familiar with this piece of our business. We will respond to you, as
soon as we receive the information from them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We thank you, in advance, for your patience.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Easy Bake Oven</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/easy-bake-oven"/>
    <updated>2003-01-17T00:00:09-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/easy-bake-oven</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Hasbro,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My daughter, Denise, was given the easy bake oven as a birthday gift recently and last weekend I decided to put it to good use. I attempted to make my famous chicken kiev dish, but after sitting down to eat it my family realized the chicken was grossly undercooked. My youngest son, Aaron, stayed up vomiting all night as a result. Is this normal? I couldn't find any solution in the FAQ for this problem. Is my easy bake oven defective? If so, how do I get a replacement?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B Wilson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Can I get the unit in blue?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Villain Supply</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/villain-supply"/>
    <updated>2002-08-09T11:21:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/villain-supply</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Villian,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm writing you concerning a certain product advertised on your website.
The product in question is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.archive.org/web/20020802142904/http://www.villainsupply.com/traps.html&quot;&gt;ULTRA-BUDGET MAN TRAP&lt;/a&gt;

Evil On A Budget, Inc. presents the Ultra-Budget Man Trap Kit. Just
dig a hole*, place these sharpened spikes in the bottom, and cover the hole
with loose branches. You have a deadly trap in just minutes!

Price: US$29.49 (Save 20%!)
* hole not included
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The hole isn't included?? For $29.49, I would think the hole must be included. Now I have to pay $29.49 for a product with no hole, and I have to make a separate purchase for a shovel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this product should be re-evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pilsbury Toaster Strudel: Reply #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/pilsbury-toaster-strudel"/>
    <updated>2002-08-02T11:20:42-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/pilsbury-toaster-strudel-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your prompt reply. I am looking forward to seeing your new and improved ad campaign. I will keep an eye out for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pilsbury Toaster Strudel: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/pilsbury-toaster-strudel"/>
    <updated>2002-08-01T00:00:47-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/pilsbury-toaster-strudel-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Ms. Wilson:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting Pillsbury.  We are sorry you were disappointed with our advertising for Pillsbury Toaster Strudel.  Our intent is to encourage both potential and existing customers to use our products.  Your opinions are important to us and will be carefully reviewed with our marketing and advertising staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We appreciate your interest and hope you continue to enjoy our products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,  &lt;br/&gt;
Julie Carlson&lt;br/&gt;
General Mills&lt;br/&gt;
Consumer Services&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pilsbury Toaster Strudel</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/pilsbury-toaster-strudel"/>
    <updated>2002-07-30T00:00:52-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/pilsbury-toaster-strudel-2</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Pilsbury,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to question the validity of a certain Pop Tarts commercial I just saw. In this particular commercial a seemingly caring mother gives her son a pop tart while pushing him out the door for school. When he meets up with his other friend, he is given a pilsbury toaster strudel and seems thankful. The other friend asks the boy &quot;So, where do you put all those pop tarts?&quot;. The boy then pulls a garage door opener out of his pocket and pushes the button. The garage door opens and reveals a mountain of Pop Tarts spilling out of the garage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, what kind of mother gives their boy a Pop Tart for breakfast? Breakfast is the most important meal of the day, and a tiny goo filled pasty does not constitute a complete breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, is that boy ready to handle the responsibility of carrying a garage door opener around? If he loses it he gives anyone access to the house. That is a very big risk that mother is taking.  Also, how did the parents not notice the pop tarts piling up in the garage?  With that sort of lack of attention, I can't imagine what else they haven't noticed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Subway: Reply 1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/subway"/>
    <updated>2002-07-26T10:15:57-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/subway-reply-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Potter,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The subway location I was reffering to is located on the corner of Victory Drive and Hoffman Road in Mankato. However, I had the same problem at the Subway on Riverfront Drive, as well as the one on Madison Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for looking into this matter,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Subway: Response #1</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/subway"/>
    <updated>2002-07-25T11:16:46-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/subway-response-1</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mrs. Wilson,
Thank you for contacting Subway.  I have received your comments and need to have a more exact location of the store you visited because there are several in the area.  Secondly, with requests for franchise information, you can call 1-800-888-4848 ext 1315 but I will also email your requests to that department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank You,  &lt;br/&gt;
Robin P-----r&lt;br/&gt;
SUBWAY ® World Headquarters&lt;br/&gt;
Customer Care Representative&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Subway</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/subway"/>
    <updated>2002-07-25T08:15:53-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/subway</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Subway,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last month I purchased what I believed to be a 6 inch veggie sub. When I got home, I measured it, and it wasn't quite 6 inches. Was this just a mistake during my visit, or are they all not quite 6 inches? I just don't want people to get shorted a single millimeter of your delicious sandwiches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I would like information on opening my own Subway location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your time,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pepsi</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/pepsi"/>
    <updated>2002-07-18T00:00:23-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/pepsi</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Pepsi,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a long hot day, I recently sat down to enjoy a crystal clear pepsi. However, upon tasting it I was shocked to find it was almost completely flat and had a funny flavor I can not describe. I know they're not SUPPOSED to taste like this which make me think the 12 pack I purchased is defective. I already tried taking it back to the store but they
informed me that they don't carry the product anymore. How do I go about getting a replacement?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>PowerAde</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/powerade"/>
    <updated>2002-07-17T16:00:20-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/powerade</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. or Ms. Powerade,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing you in concern of urination problems associated with Powerade. I recently purchased your 32. oz fruit punch, and I went to the bathroom many times because of it. I was not drinking any other beverage at the time. Is this normal? Also, I question the validity of a woman drinking powerade and then jumping over a bridge. I find that it is not possible to do, and I'm fearful for the people who are trying it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time and God bless,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda B. Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Papa Johns</title>
    <link href="http://complainist.com/letters/papa-johns"/>
    <updated>2002-07-17T11:09:52-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://complainist.com/papa-johns</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. John&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm writing to you concerning one of your advertisements I saw. You advertised your Volcano Pizza, which sounded very good to me. I decided to pick one on my way home from the Minneapolis area. When I ordered, your employees laughed like I was telling a joke. When it was clear that I was not laughing with them, they rudely told me they don't offer that pizza at this location. I left a bit distraught, as I didn't know what I'd tell my family. They were all looking forward to trying this &quot;Volcano Pizza&quot; we had heard so much about. Please let me know where or when I will be able to purchase this product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time,&lt;br/&gt;
Linda Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>